Guide to the Artists Space Collection of Artist Files MSS.506
Fales Library and Special Collections
Artists Space Collection of Artist Files
1982-2006
Fales Library and Special Collections
Artists Space (Gallery)
Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.). Library
MSS.506
78.5 linear feet in 78 record cartons and 2 half manuscript boxes
6.53 Terabytes
Artists Space is a New York City non-profit art gallery and arts organization. The organization aims to support young, emerging artists, specifically those who had not yet had a solo show in New York City. Artists Space became one of the most influential alternative non-profit arts spaces in the Downtown New York scene, hosting a variety of prominent exhibitions. This collection consists of materials submitted by artists documenting their work, including CVs, catalogues, photographic elements, correspondence, applications to Artists Space, drafts of published works, gallery floor plans and maps, grant applications, and promotional matter in the form of brochures, postcard announcements, newsletters, posters, and press releases. Artists Space events and exhibition programming are also documented through visual materials in this collection, including slides and prints, drawings, paintings and collages, and digital images. Topics covered in this collection include family, feminism, materialism, nature, and sociopolitical issues such as the AIDS crisis and society in the aftermath of 9/11. Many artists in this collection explore the ways in which culture, race, gender, and sexuality define their interactions with the world. The collection also helps document Artists' Space's function as an early pre-internet artist repository and database, and a cultural history of downtown New York City in the 1980s through the early 2000s.
Scope and Contents
Materials in the Artists Space Collection of Artists Files Collection document the participants of this art organization from the early 1980s through the early 2000s. This collection consists of materials submitted by artists documenting their work, including curriculum vitae, catalogues, photographic elements, correspondence, applications to Artists Space, drafts of published works, gallery floor plans and maps, grant applications, and promotional matter in the form of brochures, postcard announcements, newsletters, posters, and press releases. Artists Space events and exhibition programming are also documented through visual materials in this collection, including slides and prints, drawings, paintings and collages, and digital images, audio, and video recordings stored on floppy disks, zip disks, CD-Rs. The artists represented are international, with a heavy concentration of artists living in the United States.
Many artists submitted slides for the database, and later submitted CD-Rs with two images of their work to be displayed in the database. Artist statements were also submitted to the database describing the physical aspects of an artist's works, their influences, and what they were trying to convey in their art. Topics covered in this collection include family, feminism, materialism, nature, and sociopolitical issues such as the AIDS crisis and society in the aftermath of 9/11. Many artists in this collection explore the ways in which culture, race, gender, and sexuality define their interactions with the world. The collection also helps document Artists' Space's function as an early pre-internet artist repository and database, and a cultural history of downtown New York City in the 1980s through the early 2000s.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by the archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Historical Note
Artists Space (originally called the Committee on Visual Arts, Inc.) was founded in 1972 by arts administrator Trudie Grace and critic Irving Sandler as a pilot project for the New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA). The original goal of the Committee was to support young, emerging artists, specifically those who had not yet had a solo show in New York City. Quickly thereafter, Artists Space became financially independent of the State Council and over the years became one of the most influential alternative non-profit arts spaces in the Downtown New York Scene. Throughout the years Artists Space has retained its commitment to exhibiting new and experimental artworks, and has expanded its scope to include readings, panel discussions, film programs, and special series, including the International Projects Program, Selections from the Artists File, and others.
Provocative programming has been the hallmark of Artists Space throughout its history, and a variety of prominent exhibitions are well-represented in the collection, including Adrian Piper's "It's Just Art" (1981), Nan Goldin's "Witnesses: Against Our Vanishing" (1989), Douglas Crimp's "Pictures" (1977), and Michael Asher's "Untitled" (1988). "Witnesses: Against Our Vanishing" sparked controversy, when, due to an objection to an essay by David Wojnarowicz in the catalogue, the National Endowment for the Arts pulled its funding in the wake of Newt Gingrich's moral crusade in Congress. The attendant controversy is well-documented in the collection. Artists Space has also given many artists their first chance at the spotlight, amongst them: Joan Jonas, Cindy Sherman, Jeff Koons, Sherrie Levine, Louise Lawler, Laurie Anderson, Barbara Bloom, John Miller, John Baldessari, Jack Smith, Andrea Fraser, Haim Steinbach, Tim Rollins, Lyle Ashton Harris, Ashley Bickerton, Peter Halley, Lari Pittman, Group Material, Stuart Sherman, Barbara Kruger, Laurie Simmons, Anthony McCall, Fred Wilson, Felix Gonzalez-Torres, Mike Kelly, Judith Barry, Michael Smith, Robert Longo, and Jenny Holzer. For a full list of the exhibition history of the gallery, please see: http://artistsspace.org/archive
Source: Fales Library and Special Collections. "Guide to the Artists Space Archive." http://dlib.nyu.edu/findingaids/html/fales/artistsspace/bioghist.html (retrieved September 7, 2018).
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Related Materials
Artists Space Archive (MSS 291)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Jennifer Tobias of the Museum of Modern Art Library in April 2018; the accession number associated with this transfer is 2018.055. An accretion was transferred in August 2022; the accession number associated with this transfer is 2023.008.
Custodial History
Artists Space originally donated this collection to the Museum of Modern Art Library in 2006; it was transferred to the Fales Library and Special Collections at New York University in 2018.
AIDS (Disease) and art -- United States.; Sex and art.; September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001.; Color photographs.; Clippings (information artifacts); CD-Rs.; Art -- Social aspects.; Art -- New York (State) -- New York.; Art -- Exhibitions -- 20th century; Art, American -- 20th century; Art -- Exhibitions.; Artists -- United States -- 20th century; Artists and community -- United States; Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.). Library
- Abezash, 2003-2004 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Constructed World (Group of artists), 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ABC Praxis, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abe, Koya, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Abeler, Evi, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Abelow, Joshua, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Aber, Ita, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Abraham, Kristin, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 95)
- Abrams, Rachel, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Accardi, Raina, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Acharya, Dhruvi, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ackerman, Alicia, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Acosta, Jose, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Acosta Osorio, Alexander, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Adams, Jamie, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Adams, Tracey, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Addy, Silja, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Adelheim, Eric, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Adler, Beth, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Aebris, Joseph, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Aftenie, Radu, 2001-2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Agarwal, Neil, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Agnoli, Kathleen, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Agresti, Francesco, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Aguilar, Matias, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Ahmed, Tazeen, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 75)
- Ahkami, Negar, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Ahn, Jae Hi, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Ahn, Seongmin, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Ahn, Soo Yeun, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Aho, Holly, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Ahrens, June, 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- AHURA, 1996-2004 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Aige, Mar, 1996-2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Aimi, Andrea, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ainslie, Elizabeth, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Aishman, Steven, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Aissa, Raja, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Akers, Mason, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Akikography, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Akiyama, Sayaka, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Al Naqeeb, Sula, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Albee, Rick, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Albert, Elizabeth, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Alderman, Liz, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Aldrich, Lynn, 1996-2003 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Alexander, Bette, 1995-2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Alexander, Olga, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Alexander Frater, Jean, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Alexis, Michel, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Alibrandi, Elaine, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Alic, Amanda, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Allannic, Cyrille, 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Allen, David, 1997-2004 (Box 61, Folder 74)
- Allen, Jane Ingram, 1988-1998 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Allen, Jonathan, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 84)
- Allen, Jonathan, 2002-2005 (Box 61, Folder 83)
- Allen, Meredith, 1990-1995 (Box 61, Folder 73)
- Allen, Nanci, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Allen, Pamella, 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Alleyne, Armando, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Alling, Janet, 1972-2001 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Allison, Caroline, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Aloma, Lilyan, 1992-2001 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Altamura, Mauro, 2002-2005 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Alugas, Eric, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Alvarado, Celina, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Alvarez, Cristina, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Alward, Sharon, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Alwast, Peter, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Amano, Fumiko, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Amaturo, Festina, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Amesbury, Robert, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Amir, Mughal, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 72)
- Ammons, Linda, 1983-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Amorim, Elka, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Amoros, Grimanesa, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Anastasi, Audrey, 1996-2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Ancalmo, Carlos, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Andersen-Warren, Jaimie, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Anderson, Frank, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Anderson, Heather, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Anderson, Judith, 2000-2003 (Box 61, Folder 86)
- Anderson, Kristin, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Anderson, Todd, 2002-2003 (Box 61, Folder 85)
- Ando, Yuichiro, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Ando Stanoff, Miya, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Andrade, Carlos, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Andranowski, Barbara, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Andrews, Ethan, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Andrews, Jonathan, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Andrews, Karen, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Andrews, Kevin Clay, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Anfinson, Erin, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Angelaius (Lungleg), Antonia E., 1997 (Box 61, Folder 76)
- Angelopoulos, Elaine, 1988-2005 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Angio, Alex, 1992-2005 (Box 61, Folder 71)
- Annenberg, Marcia, 1996-2005 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Annesanti, Carlo, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Ansel, Eric, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Antar, Robin, 1998-2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Aoki, Kathy, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Aoki, Miyako, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Apfelbaum, Sally, 1992-2001 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Apicella-Hitchcock, Stephan, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Apparition, M., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Appel, Genie, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Appel, Theo, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Appleton, Robert, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Aragon, Jason, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Aranita, Jeffrey du'Vallier, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Araujo, Michele, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Araya, Kinga, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Arbel, Noa, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Archer, Clover, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Ard, Carolyn, 1995-2001 (Box 63, Folder 32)
- Arena, Meredith, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Arena, Susan, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Arias, Soledad, 2000-2007 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Armetta, Amoreen, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Armstead, Kenseth, 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Armusik, Eric, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Arndt, Dianne, 1983-1999 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Arnold, Catherine, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Arnold, Jean, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Arnold, Kathryn, 1999-2005 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Arnold, Lee, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Arnold, Matthew, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Arnold, Sophie, 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Aronowitz, Irving, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Aronson, Yelena, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Arroni, Oudi, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 96)
- Arsenault, David, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Arsenault, Todd, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Arthur, Margaret, 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Arthurs, Madeleine, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Artist, Suicide, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Asbury, Katrin, 1997-2001 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Ascalon, David, 1992-2002 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Ashe, Beverley, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Aslandis, John, 1999-2001 (Box 64, Folder 102)
- Assed, Barry, 1998-2004 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Assefi, Raoof, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Aster, Joshua, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Astor, Sonia, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Astor, Ted, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Atkisson, Valerie, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Ator, Kirsten, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Attias, Ronit, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Auboiron, Michelle, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Auge, Carl, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Augenblick, Kate, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Aurandt, Eric, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Aurich, Carla, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Avedisian, Donna A., 1998 (Box 63, Folder 33)
- Avila, Miguel Angel, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Avramovic, Dora, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Avruch, Carla, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Axelsdottir, Hronn, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Aylon, Helene, 1982-2001 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Ayoung, Todd, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Ayres, Derek, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Azadeh, Azadeh, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Azurdia, Javier, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Babb, Elizabeth, 1997-2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Babin, Myriam, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 34)
- Bach, Tuyet, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Bache-Wiig, Tom, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Bachhuber, Nina Lola, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Bachi, Michal, 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Bacon, Pat, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bacon, Sara Heart, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bacos, Nina, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Badenhausen, La Thoriel, 1999-2001 (Box 63, Folder 36)
- Baer, Adam, 1991-2004 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Baer, Julie, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Bagot, Clement, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Bagshaw, Barbara, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Bahl, Shelly, 1994-2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Baik, Sung, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Bailey, Christine, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Bailey, Xenobia, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Baillie, Alan, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 35)
- Bain, Kevin, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Baines, Steven, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Baity, G. Scott, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Bajor, Lois H., 1998-2005 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Bak, Rick, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Baker, David, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 37)
- Baker, Jessica, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Baker, Joy D., 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Baker, Melanie, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Baker, Nancy, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Baker, R.C., 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Balas, Jack, 1998-2005 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Baldwin, Ned, 1996-2004 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Baldwin, Richard, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Baldwin, Sheila, 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Balisle, Jenny E., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Balmat, Jasmine, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Balmuth, Laurie, 1995-2000 (Box 63, Folder 38)
- Bang, Woo Song, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Bangs, C, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Bangs, James, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Baranowski, Kim, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Barayazarra, Zigor, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Barber, Daniel, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Barbush, Gennadi, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Bardyshevsky, Inda, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Barich, Steven R., 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Baricsa, Marta, 1997-2002 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Barnard, Anne N., 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Barnes, Jeffrey, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Barnes, Julia, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Barr, Olivia, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Barras, Lindsay, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Barrett, Peter, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Barry, Mark, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Bartels, Cathy, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Bartels, Heike, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Bartossik, Nikolai, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Basman, Charles, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Bassis, Aileen, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Bastide Duarte, Frederica, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Bateman, Lisa, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Bateman, William, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Batista Lorenzo, Nieves, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Batiste, Sheila, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Batt, Deborah, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Batten, Karin, 1995-2005 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Battenfield, Jackie, 1999-2004 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Battis, Nicholas, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Battle, Laura, 1989-2000 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Batu, Suzan, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Bauer, Sarah, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Baumann, Richard, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Bauta, Yovani, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Baxter, Deborah, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 93)
- Bay, Amy, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Bayliss, Sean, 1992-2000 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Beal, Justin, 2003-2005 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Beal, Kristin, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Beall, Karen, 1994-2004 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Beallor, Fran, 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Beaumont, Sarah-Kate, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Beausoleil, Kathleen, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Beblo, Deborah, 1992-2002 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Bechrakis, Venia, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Beck, Anne, 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Beck, Deborah, 1989-1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Beck, Kim, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Beck, Michelle, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Beck and Calvo, Michelle and Jorge, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Beck, Tad, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Becker, Chris, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Becker, K.C., 2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Becker, Sandra, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 39)
- Beckles, Ken, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Behbahani, Bahar, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Beldner, Ray, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Beldon, Lora, 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Belhache, Philippe, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Bell, Laura, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Bell, Laura Ann, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Bell, Lola, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Bellavia, Timothy, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Bellici, Michelle, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Bellinger, Len, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Belloff, Mindy, 1986-1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Bellum, Shannon, 2001-2005 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Ben-Adi, Niv, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Ben-Haim, Zigi, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Ben-Shitrit, Orit, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Benarcik, Susan, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Bendheim, Fred, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Benedict, Scott, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Benedis, Sheila, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Benes, Marian, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Benjamins, Jani, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Bennett, Doug, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Bennett, Gretchen, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Bennett, Lisa, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Benton, Sallie, 1978-2000 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Bentz, Rosetta, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Beorn, Coen, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Berberian, Taleen, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Berelson, Howard, 1989-2001 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Berenbaum, Fabian, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Berengolc, Milenka, 1996-2001 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Berg, Siri, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Bergensten, Audrey, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Bergenthal, Vivian, 1992-2001 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Berger, Neil, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Bergesen, Jean Alison, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Bergh, Neil, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Bergman, Dan, 1992-2003 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Bergmann, Meredith, 1982-2001 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Berk, Jed, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Berkeley, Pernel, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Berklich, Jennifer, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Berkowitz, Michael, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Berlin, Alejandro, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Berlin, Daniel, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Berlin, Ragna, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Bermudez, Sandra, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Bernberg, Lana, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Berner, Reina, 1992-2001 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Bernier, Tina, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Berning, Mary, 2001-2004 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Bernstein, Audry, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Bernstein, Michael, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Berrigan, Caitlin, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Berry, Alison, 1994-2001 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Bertiller, Gabriela, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Bertuzzi, Roger-Luis, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Berzinski, Jon, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Besl, Amanda, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Besseteaux, Martine, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Bettaglio, Elia, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Betts, William, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Beuhler, Launa, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Beveridge, Stephen, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Bezzubov, Sasha, 1997-2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Bialas, Marshall, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Bidwa, Laura, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Biederman, Gail, 1986-2005 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Bieltvedt, Arnor, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Bilger, Humphrey, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Billings, Michelle, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Binikos, Ektoras, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Biondo, Sarah, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Birch, Alan, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Bird, Rebecca, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Bird, Stephanie, 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Bird, Steven, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 101)
- Bis, Marc, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Bisbee, Michael, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Bischoff, Robert, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Bishop, Brian, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Bishop, Lyn, 1998-2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Bishop, Naomi, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Bissaillon, Kristen, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Bisson, Mariella, 1998-2003 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Bitterolf, Stephen, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Bjerneruf, Marcus, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Black, Ana, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Black, Darrell, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Blackey, Mary, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Blaimont, Sylvette, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Blair, Justin, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Blake, Paul, 1986-1996 (Box 63, Folder 40)
- Blasco, Isidro, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Blasor, Lorraine, 1999-2005 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Blazina, Jennifer, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Bleeker, Annemarie, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Bliss, Matthew, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Blizard, Christie, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Bloch, Janet, 1993-2001 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Block, Brian, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Block, Tom, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 39)